brandbucket.com 2016-05-05

# Privacy Policy | BrandBucket

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When purchasing or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. 
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you. 
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests. 
  * To administer a survey or other site feature. 
  * To quickly process your transactions. 
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. 

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders 
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred 

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the instructions at the bottom of each email. Keep in mind if you wish to terminate your registered account with our service you can do so by emailing us. 

### How do we protect visitor information?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored on our servers.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to target ads to you on other websites. 

We use cookies to:

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits. 
  * Keep track of advertisements. 
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. You can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. If you disable cookies, some features on our site may be disabled. 

### Third Party Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at [info@brandbucket.com](mailto:info@brandbucket.com)

Last Edited on October 12, 2015
